https://www.austwinetourco.com.au/privacy/

Contact Us
About UsbackMeet the TeamLinks ToursbackDay TourPremium TourOvernight StaysCorporate & Social DaysBallooning & Wine TourTown, Coast and Country SeriesWestern Victoria Ultimate Food and Wine EscapeGift Vouchers GalleriesbackTour VideoHot Air BallooningDomaine Chandon WineryPunt Road WinesBalgownie EstateSoumah WinesYering StationYering FarmDay TourPremium TourOvernight TourGroup Tour Reviews InformationbackFAQsTerms & ConditionsPrivacy Policy Blog Contact Us
Menu
Privacy
Privacy Statement
Australian Wine Tour Company Pty Ltd views the protection of your privacy as an integral part of its commitment towards complete accountability and integrity in all its activities and programs. This commitment is supported by the new laws dealing with personal information about you that is stored or received by Australian Wine Tour Company. Consequently, we will:
Only use personal information provided by you for the purposes for which it was collected and for any other authorised use
Not disclose your personal information to a third party and will take all necessary measures to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure
Ensure that your personal information is not disclosed to other institutions and authorities except if required or authorised by law
Security Statement
Australian Wine Tour Company have established an online eCommerce system with RealTime payment options. This is undertaken with Verisign.com.au and all online transfer of sensitive details will be via their highly secure website. See below for a brief description of the VeriSign process and their data storage capabilities, or download the Versign Australia’s Public Security policy in PDF format.
Centralised and Secure Data Management
Data is hosted in VeriSign’s high-security, fully redundant, risk-free data center. All transactions between consumers and VeriSign occur over secure SSL connections.
How secure is the VeriSign payment platform?
A critical concern for electronic commerce is the secure transmission of data. To protect consumer data during transmission, VeriSign uses the latest SSL encryption technology that securely passes transaction data to the VeriSign gateway. However, an even bigger security threat to electronic commerce is the storage of sensitive data. To prevent data compromise in the storage server, VeriSign stores sensitive transaction information on secure systems that cannot be accessed through the Internet. Furthermore, VeriSign uses hardware and software firewall technology and additional encryption technology to eliminate all opportunity for intruders to break into a server and compromise information.
Back to the top
